Guide to the Harriet Wasserman Literary Agency Records, 1940s-2000 and undated (bulk 1978-1995) RL.00509
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings Series, A-Z, 1941-1995
  - Writings (Open) Subseries, A-Z, 1948-1995 and undated
    - Bellow, Saul
      - The Civilized Barbarian Reader (print), 1987 March 18 (Box WO-2)
      - Cloister Culture, 1966 (Box WO-2)
      - A Comment On Form and Despair, 1964 (Box WO-2)
      - Cousins, 1983 [July?] - December, 4 folders (Box WO-2)
      - Culture Now: Some Animadversions, Some Laughs, 1971-1993, 4 folders of which 3 are print (Box WO-2)
      - The Day They Signed the Treaty (print), 1979 April 1 (Box WO-2)
    - Bellow, Saul (continued) (Box WO-3)
      - The Dean's December, 1981-, 6 versions in 10 folders; version 6 is a French translation (Box WO-3)
      - Deep Readers of the World, Beware! undated (Box WO-3)
      - Distractions of a Fiction Writer (print), undated (Box WO-3)
      - Dreiser and the Triumph of Art (print), undated (Box WO-3)
      - Facts That Put Fancy To Flight, 1962 (Box WO-3)
      - A Father-To-Be (print), undated (Box WO-3)
      - Foreword to An Age of Enormity: Life and Writing in the Forties and Fifties by Issac Rosenfeld, 1962 (Box WO-3)
      - Foreword to The Rebellion of the Masses (print), by Jose Ortega Y Gasset, 1985 (Box WO-3)
      - The French as Dostoevsky Saw Them (print), 1955 (Box WO-3)
      - Gide as Writer and Autobiographer (print), undated (Box WO-3)
      - The Good Place (print), 1990 July (Box WO-3)
      - Harold Rosenberg (print), 1979 October (Box WO-3)
      - Henderson the Rain King (print, in Russian), 1991 (Box WO-3)
      - Herzog (from Lois Phillips files), undated (Box WO-3)
        For further information about Phillips files see Correspondence (Open) Subseries, Bellow, 1985 and that subseries' note)
      - Herzog Visits Chicago, 1964 August 8-15, print; See Oversize Material Boxes (Box WO-3)
      - Him With His Foot in His Mouth, 1983-1984, 3 versions in 4 folders (Box WO-3)
      - Him With His Foot in His Mouth, 1982 Nov., 2 folders; folder 2 is print (Box WO-3)
      - How I Wrote Augie March's Story, 1954 (Box WO-3)
      - Humboldt's Gift, undated, 3 folders (Box WO-3)
    - Bellow, Saul (continued) (Box WO-4)
      - Humboldt's Gift, 1973-1975 and undated, 15 folders; boxes 16-18 are 1973-75; 17 and 18 are print. See also Oversize Material Boxes). (Box WO-4)
      - An Interview With Myself (print), 1975 (Box WO-4)
      - In the Days of Mr. Roosevelt, ca. 1983, 5 versions, 1 print (Box WO-4)
      - Introduction to The Closing of the American Mind, by Allan Bloom, ca. 1986, 3 folders, folder 3 print (Box WO-4)
      - Isaac Rosenfeld, 1956 (Box WO-4)
      - Italian Fiction: Without Hope (print), undated (Box WO-4)
      - It All Adds Up, 1993, 6 versions in 11 folders (Box WO-4)
      - The Jefferson Lectures, 1977 (Box WO-4)
      - John Berryman, Friend, 1973, 3 versions, 1 print (Box WO-4)
      - Joyce's Ulysses: A Personal View, undated (Box WO-4)
      - The Last Analysis, undated, 2 folders (Box WO-4)
      - Laughter in the Ghetto, 1953 (Box WO-4)
      - Literary Notes on Khrushchev (print), 1961 (Box WO-4)
      - Literature (print), 1963 (Box WO-4)
        (N.B.: appears to have been pub. in Mortimer Adler's Great Ideas Today)
      - Literature in the Age of Technology, ca. 1973-74, 3 folders; folders 2 and 3 print (Box WO-4)
      - A Matter of the Soul, 1975, 2 folders, folder 2 print (Box WO-4)
    - Bellow, Saul (continued) (Box WO-5)
      - Memoirs of a Bootlegger's Son, 1992 August, 4 folders (Box WO-5)
      - Mind Over Chatter, 1965 (Box WO-5)
      - The Modern Religious Novel, undated (Box WO-5)
      - More Die of Heartbreak, 19 versions in 20 folders (Box WO-5)
      - Mozart (print), 1992 Spring (Box WO-5)
      - My Man Bummidge, undated (Box WO-5)
      - Nobel Lecture, 1976-77, 5 pieces print and typescript (Box WO-5)
    - Bellow, Saul (continued) (Box WO-6)
      - Occasional Pieces, ca. 1982, 9 folders (Box WO-6)
      - Old Paris (print), 1984 (Box WO-6)
      - On Fact and Feeling in the Novel, 1959 October (Box WO-6)
      - On John Cheever (print), 1983 February 17 (Box WO-6)
      - Paris, Then and Now, 1982 November 17 (Box WO-6)
      - The Perils of Pleasing the Public (print), 1968 (Box WO-6)
      - The Sealed Treasure (print), undated (Box WO-6)
      - A Silver Dish 1978-79 and undated, 6 folders, folders 4-5 print (Box WO-6)
    - Bellow, Saul (continued) (Box WO-7)
      - Skepticism and the Depth of Life (print), 1967 (Box WO-7)
      - Some Notes on Recent American Fiction (print), 1963 (Box WO-7)
      - Some Questions and Answers (print), 1975-1976 (Box WO-7)
      - Something To Remember Me By, 1991 and undated, 5 folders (Box WO-7)
      - Something To Remember Me By, 1990 and undated, 12 folders (Box WO-7)
        Folders 9-12 print; folders 11-12 Italian and Japanese translations.
      - Starting Out In Chicago, 1974, 3 folders; folder 2 print (Box WO-7)
      - Talk at Allen Bloom's Funeral Service, October 9 1992 (Box WO-7)
      - A Talk With the Yellow Kid, (print), 1956 and 1993, 2 folders (Box WO-7)
      - A Theft, 1988 February 25, 1 folder (Box WO-7)
    - Bellow, Saul (continued) (Box WO-8)
      - A Theft, 1988 and undated, 9 folders (Box WO-8)
      - There Is Simply Too Much To Think About (print), 1992 September 14 from To Jerusalem and Back, (print) 1976 July 19 (Box WO-8)
      - Two Morning Monologues (print), 1941 May-June (Box WO-8)
      - What Americans Read and Hear is 'Crisis Chatter' (print), 1976 December 5 (Box WO-8)
      - What Kind of Day Did You Have? undated (Box WO-8)
      - Where Do We Go From Here: The Future of Fiction (print), undated (Box WO-8)
      - White House and Artists (print), 1962 (Box WO-8)
      - Why Not? 1978 and undated, 4 folders; folder 4 print (Box WO-8)
      - Winter in Tuscany (print), 1992 November (Box WO-8)
      - A World Too Much With Us (print), 1975 Autumn (Box WO-8)
      - The Writer as Moralist (print), 1963 (Box WO-8)
      - A Writer From Chicago, 1981-82 and undated, 6 folders (Box WO-8)
      - Writers and Literature In America, 1975 (Box WO-8)
      - Writers, Intellectuals, Politics: Mainly Reminiscence, 1993 April 6 (Box WO-8)
      - Zetland: By a Character Witness (print), undated (Box WO-8)
    - Biddle, Wayne
      - America's Weapon Makers and How They Grew (print), 1988 Summer (Box WO-8)
      - Barons of the Sky, undated, 1 version in 3 folders (Box WO-8)
      - Cold War Resartus (print), 1990 October 24 (Box WO-8)
      - Corporations on Campus (print), 1987 July 24 (Box WO-8)
      - The Deception of Detection (print), 1986 March (Box WO-8)
      - The Endless Countdown (print), 1980 June 22 (Box WO-8)
      - The Eyes Have It (print), 1983 June (Box WO-8)
      - Facing the Hazards of the Nuclear Age (print), 1982 January 24 (Box WO-8)
      - High Art, Low Art, No Art (print), 1979 Summer (Box WO-8)
      - How America Eagerly Built Her Arsenal (print), 1988 Fall (Box WO-8)
      - It Must Be Simple (print), 1986 June (Box WO-8)
      - Mediterranean Holiday (print), 1981 January 4 (Box WO-8)
      - Neutron Bomb: An Explosive Issue, (print), 1981 November 15 (Box WO-8)
      - The Real Secret of the Stealth (print), 1986 February (Box WO-8)
      - Restocking the Chemical Arsenal (print), 1981 (Box WO-8)
      - The Selling of D'Aubisson (print), 1982 July 24-31 (Box WO-8)
      - Silicon Valley Days (print), 1981 June (Box WO-8)
      - The Silo Busters: Misguided Missiles-The MX Project (print), 1979 December (Box WO-8)
      - Skeleton Alleged In the Stealth Bomber's Closet (print), 1989 May 12 (Box WO-8)
      - 'Star Wars' Technology: It's More Than a Fantasy (print), 1985 March 5 (Box WO-8)
      - Star Wars: The Dream (print), 1987 July (Box WO-8)
      - Who's Counting (print), 1987 August 29 (Box WO-8)
      - The Wizard of Jodrell Bank (print), 1986 September 14 (Box WO-8)
    - Bloom, Allan
      - The Closing of the American Mind, 1986, 1 version in 2 folders (Box WO-8)
      - Harvard Lecture, 1988 December 14 (Box WO-8)
      - Liberty, Equality, Sexuality, an extract from The Closing of the American Mind (print), 1987 December (Box WO-8)
      - Love and Friendship, 1991 September- October, 1 version in 3 folders (Box WO-8)
    - Bloom, Allan (Box WO-9)
      - Love and Friendship, 1992-93, 8 versions in 23 folders (Box WO-9)
      - Our Listless University Students, undated (Box WO-9)
      - Rousseau and the Arts in Modernity, 1983-84 (Box WO-9)
      - Untitled Lecture at L'Agora, 1988 April 7 (Box WO-9)
    - Bloomstein, Henry
      - The Brothers Kresky, 1984 March 6 (Box WO-9)
      - Good Behavior, 1984 June 18 (Box WO-9)
    - Bolton, Ruthie
      - Gal: A True Life, 1 folder (Box WO-9)
    - Bolton, Ruthie (Box WO-10)
      - Gal: A True Life, 1994 and undated, 3 versions in 4 folders (Box WO-10)
    - Brown, Wesley
      - Boogie Woogie and Booker T., undated (Box WO-10)
      - The Darktown Strutters, undated (Box WO-10)
    - Buechner, Frederick
      - Brendan ( A World of Crowns) (Box WO-10)
      - The Clown in the Belfry, 2 folders (Box WO-10)
      - Now and Then (Box WO-10)
      - The Son of Laughter, undated, 1 version in 2 folders (Box WO-10)
      - The Truth of Stories (print), 1992 January-February (Box WO-10)
      - The Wizard's Tide, 1989 April 6 (Box WO-10)
    - Cable, Mary
      - Blizzard of '88 (print), 1988 March (Box WO-10)
    - Clark, Eleanor
      - Camping Out, undated, 1 version in 3 folders (Box WO-10)
      - The Fortress and Raggedy Ann (print), 1992 Spring (Box WO-10)
      - Monday We Change Our Clothes (print), 1979 (Box WO-10)
    - Crasta, Richard
      - The Revised Kama Sutra, undated, 2 folders (Box WO-10)
    - DeHaven, Tom
      - Freaks' Amour, 1985 October (Box WO-10)
    - Donohue, H.E.F.
      - Safe Home, 1958-1970, 6 printed extracts (Box WO-10)
    - Fields, Maxine
      - Baby Names From Around the World, 2 versions in 3 folders (Box WO-10)
    - Gertler, T. (Box WO-11)
      - Elbowing the Seducer, 2 folders (Box WO-11)
      - The Quiet Man (print), 1986 July (Box WO-11)
      - Your Mother Had a Gorgeous Alligator (print), 1984 November (Box WO-11)
    - Goldstein, Rebecca
      - The Dark Sister, 1989 and undated, 3 version in 5 folders (Box WO-11)
      - Mazel 1992-95 and undated, 6 versions in 8 folders (Box WO-11)
      - The Mind-Body Problem, 1982and 1990, 2 folders (Box WO-11)
      - Strange Attractors, undated, 1 version in 2 folders (Box WO-11)
    - Greenwald, Sheila
      - A Bubble of Note (print), 1980 July (Box WO-11)
      - The Bubble and the Revenge of the Bubble (print), 1975 April (Box WO-11)
      - The Dance (print), 1976 September (Box WO-11)
      - Double Bubble (print), 1977 August (Box WO-11)
      - Here's Hermione, 3 folders (Box WO-11)
      - A Story in Pictures (print), 1974 March (Box WO-11)
      - A Story in Pictures (print), 1975 April (Box WO-11)
      - The Umbrella (print), 1975 November (Box WO-11)
    - Hassler, Jon
      - A Green Journey, undated, 1 version in 2 folders (Box WO-11)
    - Hassler, Jon (continued) (Box WO-12)
      - Simon's Night, undated (Box WO-12)
    - Heller, Erica
      - Splinters, 3 folders (Box WO-12)
    - Hijuelos, Oscar
      - The Fourteen Sisters of Emilio Montez O'Brien, 6 versions in 17 folders (Box WO-12)
    - Hijuelos, Oscar (continued) (Box WO-13)
      - The Fourteen Sisters of Emilio Montez O'Brien, 17 folders (Box WO-13)
      - The Mambo Kings Play Songs of Love, undated and 1991, 10 versions in 16 folders, author-corrected paperback printing (Box WO-13)
    - Horwitz, James
      - Cairo's Exotic Camel Market (print), undated (Box WO-13)
      - The French Foreign (print), undated (Box WO-13)
      - Magic Carpets of Secaucus, 1992 December 6 (Box WO-13)
      - The 6,000 Year of Vacation (print), undated (Box WO-13)
    - Humphreys, Josephine (Box WO-14)
      - Advice to Young Women (print), undated (Box WO-14)
      - Charleston, S.C. (print), 1988 Summer (Box WO-14)
      - The Fireman's Fair, undated, 5 versions in 10 folders (Box WO-14)
      - Moments and Memories (print), 1993 (Box WO-14)
      - New York: Two Temples of Glorious Books, (print), 1994 September 18 (Box WO-14)
    - Jhabvala, Ruth (Box WO-15)
      - Disinheritance, undated, 3 folders (Box WO-15)
      - The Englishwoman (print), undated (Box WO-15)
      - Expiation, 1980 June 9 (Box WO-15)
      - The Europeans, undated (Box WO-15)
      - Poet and Dancer, undated, 2 folders (Box WO-15)
      - Shards of Memory, undated (Box WO-15)
      - A Summer By the Sea, 1978, 2 folders; folder 2 print (Box WO-15)
      - Tradition, 1981 January (Box WO-15)
    - Jonnes, Jill
      - Living With Microwaves (print), 1980 June 9 (Box WO-15)
      - To Stay Alive, Big-City Churches Find New Roles (print), 1981 January (Box WO-15)
      - We're Still Here: The Rise, Fall and Resurrection of the South Bronx, 1983 and undated, 7 folders (Box WO-15)
    - Kennan, George Frost
      - Acceptance speech on receiving the Gold Medal for History of the American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters, 1984 May 16, 2 folders (Box WO-15)
      - Address on the occasion of his receiving the Albert Einstein Peace Prize, 1981 May 19, 2 printings (Box WO-15)
      - Address on the occasion of his receiving the Friedenspreis des Deutschen Buchhandels, 1982 October 10, 2 folders; folder 2 print (Box WO-15)
      - Address on the occasion of his receiving the Grenville Clark Prize (print), 1981 November 16 (Box WO-15)
      - Address to Union Theological Seminary on October 25, 1982 (Box WO-15)
      - After the Cold War, 1989, 3 printings (Box WO-15)
      - An Agenda for Improving Relations Between the U.S. and the U.S.S.R. (print), 1984 January/February (Box WO-15)
      - America and Russia: The Roots of Conflict, 1982 November, 2 folders; folder 2 print (Box WO-15)
      - America and the Russian Future (print), 1990 Spring (Box WO-15)
      - American Diplomacy, Foreword for expanded edition, 1984 September (Box WO-15)
      - American Diplomacy, Grinnell Lectures, 1984 January-February, 3 folders (Box WO-15)
      - America's Unstable Soviet Policy (print), 1982 November (Box WO-15)
      - Around the Cragged Hill, 1991-1992, 3 versions in 5 folders (Box WO-15)
      - As the Kremlin Sees It, 1982 January (Box WO-15)
      - The Balkan Crisis--1913 and 1993, 1993, 2 folders; folder 2 is print (Box WO-15)
      - Before the Storm (forward) by Marion Donhoff, 1990 April (Box WO-15)
      - Bemerkungen über den Doppelbeschluss, 1983 March 25 (Box WO-15)
      - The Bishops' Letter (print), 1983 May 1 (Box WO-15)
      - Blashfield Address for delivery at the Annual Ceremonial of the American Academy of Arts and Letters, May 21, 1986, 3 folders (Box WO-15)
    - Kennan, George Frost (continued) (Box WO-16)
      - Breaking the Spell (print), ca. 1983 (Box WO-16)
      - The Buried Past (print), 1988 October 27 (Box WO-16)
      - By the Light of the Midnight Sun, 1984-1985, 2 folders, 1 print (Box WO-16)
      - A Christian's View of the Arms Race (print), 1982 April 27 (Box WO-16)
      - Collected Essays, undated (Box WO-16)
      - Communism in Russian History, 1990, 2 folders, 1 print (Box WO-16)
      - Containment Then and Now, 1985, 2 folders, 1 print (Box WO-16)
      - The Curios Monsieur Cyon (print), 1986 Autumn (Box WO-16)
      - The Decline of Bismarck's World Order (print excerpt), 1979 (Box WO-16)
      - Denuclearization (print), 1981 October 11 (Box WO-16)
      - Empire of the Czar (introduction), 1988 November (Box WO-16)
      - An Exchange With George Kennan, 1983 October (Box WO-16)
      - The Fateful Alliance (epilogue), 1983 August (Box WO-16)
      - First Things First at the Summit, 1985 October - November (Box WO-16)
      - Flashbacks, 1984-1985, 4 folders, 1 print (Box WO-16)
      - For Russian Troops, A House To Go Home To, 1992-1993, 2 folders, 1 print (Box WO-16)
      - From the Past to the Future Through the Present: Conversations with Historians at the Institute for Advanced Study (print), 1992 January 10-11 (Box WO-16)
      - The G.O.P. Won the Cold War? Ridiculous, 1992 October (Box WO-16)
      - The Gorbachev Prospect (print), 1988 January 21 (Box WO-16)
      - History, Literature, and the Road to Peterhof (print), 1986 June 29 (Box WO-16)
      - The History of Arnold Toynbee, 1988-1989, 2 folders, 1 print (Box WO-16)
      - If the Kremlin Can't Rule (print), 1994 February 3 (Box WO-16)
      - In the American Mirror (print), 1986 November 6 (Box WO-16)
      - Inching Away from the Danger Zone, 1983 October 6 (Box WO-16)
      - Interview, with Robert MacNeil, 1988 December 23 (Box WO-16)
      - Is the Cold War Over? 1989 January 11 (Box WO-16)
      - Jaruzelski's Course-The Polish Crisis, 1982 January (Box WO-16)
      - Just Another Great Power (print), 1989 April 9 (Box WO-16)
      - Keeping the Faith (print), 1992 September 24 (Box WO-16)
      - The Last Wise Man: Sketches from a Life (print), 1989 April (Box WO-16)
      - The Marshall Plan and the Future of Europe, 1987-1988, 4 folders; folder 4 is print (Box WO-16)
      - Memoirs I and II (Epilogue II), 1983 April (Box WO-16)
      - The Mission in Moscow (2 folders; folder 2 is print), 1987 and undated (Box WO-16)
      - Morality and Foreign Policy (5 folders; folder 4 is print), 1985-1987 (Box WO-16)
      - New Agenda for a Weary Empire (print), 1989 December (Box WO-16)
      - A New Philosophy of Defense (print), 1986 February 13 (Box WO-16)
      - The Nuclear Delusion (excerpts, 2 folders), 1982-1983 (Box WO-16)
      - On Russian Diplomacy in the 19th Century and the Origins of World War I (3 folders), 1985-1986 (Box WO-16)
      - Pathology of Power, by Norman Cousins (foreword), 1986 May 2 (Box WO-16)
      - The President's Choice: Star Wars or Arms Control (print), 1984 Winter (Box WO-16)
      - Reducing Tensions (print), 1984 January 15 (Box WO-16)
      - Reflections on the Walgreen Lectures (print), undated (Box WO-16)
      - Remarks for the Milwaukee Forum, May 12, 1990 (print) (Box WO-16)
      - Remarks for Smithsonian Dinner, Nov. 15, 1983 (2 versions), 1983-1984 (Box WO-16)
      - Response to Pacem in Terris Award, 1982 May 11 (Box WO-16)
      - Review of The Cycles American History by Arthur M. Schlesinger, Jr., 1986 August 29 (Box WO-16)
      - Review of Gromyko Diaries for The New York Review of Books, 1988 July (Box WO-16)
      - Review of Perestroika: New Thinking for Our Country and the World for The New York Review of Books, 1987 December 10 (Box WO-16)
      - Review of Summer Meditations by Vaclav Havel, 1982 August, 2 versions (Box WO-16)
      - Review of The Uses of Adversity by Timothy Garton Ash, 1982 January and 1982 March (Box WO-16)
      - Somalia, Through a Glass Darkly (print), 1993 September 30 (Box WO-16)
      - The State Department Policy Planning Staff Papers 1947 (Foreword), 1983 July 13 (Box WO-16)
      - State of the Relations, remarks at the Smithsonian Institutions 50th Anniversary Dinner (print), 1984 January (Box WO-16)
      - The State of U.S.-Soviet Relations, (2 folders; folder 2 is print) 1983 March 17 (Box WO-16)
      - Statement before the Senate Foreign Relations Committee, Jan. 17, 1990 (Box WO-16)
      - Toward Peace on Two Fronts (print), 1982 December 13 (Box WO-16)
      - Tribute to Glenway Wescott, for delivery at the American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters, Dec. 4, 1987 (Box WO-16)
      - Trust as a Factor in International Relations, 1946 October 1 (Box WO-16)
      - Two Letters (4 folders; folder 4 is print), 1984 July-September (Box WO-16)
      - Two Views of the Soviet Problem (print), 1981 November 2 (Box WO-16)
      - The United States and the Soviet Union, 1917-1976 (print), 1976 July (Box WO-16)
      - Washington and the Baltics, 1991 January 29 (Box WO-16)
      - Why Not Peace? (print), 1983 April (Box WO-16)
      - World War I; Then, II; Then..., 1984 November (Box WO-16)
      - The Wrong Way to Treat Moscow (print), 1985 February-March (Box WO-16)
      - Zero Options (print), 1983 May 13 (Box WO-16)
      - Untitled, for The New Yorker, 1984 February-March (Box WO-16)
      - Untitled, excerpt from The Marquis de Custine and His Russia in 1839, 1988 May (Box WO-16)
      - Untitled, for The New York Times, 1984 October-November (Box WO-16)
      - Untitled, for The New York Times Magazine, 1984 January (Box WO-16)
      - Untitled, for 0, 1983 October-November (Box WO-16)
      - Untitled, undated (Box WO-16)
    - Klein, Kenneth
      - You Might Save Someone's Life Someday, undated (Box WO-16)
    - Koperwas, Sam
      - The Flash Effect, 2 folders (Box WO-16)
    - Krahn, Fernando
      - Alex Pumpernickel (Box WO-16)
      - Alex Pumpernickel in a Sticky Situation (print), 1982 April (Box WO-16)
      - Alex Pumpernickel in Over His Head (print), 1982 January (Box WO-16)
      - Alex Pumpernickel Larger Than Life (print), 1984 January (Box WO-16)
      - Alex Pumpernickel Takes the Cake (print), 1983 September (Box WO-16)
      - Secret in the Dungeon, undated (Box WO-16)
      - Sleep Tight, Alex Pumpernickel, undated (Box WO-16)
    - Kreyling, Michael
      - Author and Agent: Eudora Welty and Diarmuid Russell 1988 August-December, 2 versions in 3 folders (Box WO-16)
    - Kuskin, Karla
      - A Cat I Know (print), 1976 October (Box WO-16)
      - Said in September (print), 1976 September (Box WO-16)
    - Lansbury, Coral
      - Opium! 1988-1991, 1 version in 1 folder (Box WO-16)
    - Lansbury, Coral (continued) (Box WO-17)
      - Opium! (continued), 1988-1991, 1 version in 2 folders (Box WO-17)
      - Sweet Alice, 1983 November 25 (Box WO-17)
    - Lee, Laurel
      - Walking Through the Fire (print), 1977 May 31 (Box WO-17)
    - Lindbergh, Anne
      - Miscellaneous Poems, undated (Box WO-17)
      - Next Time, Take Care, 1986 March and undated, 2 folders (Box WO-17)
      - The Sidney Solution, undated (Box WO-17)
      - Travel Far, Pay No Fare, undated (Box WO-17)
    - Markus, Julia
      - American Rose excerpt, Getting the Last Word, undated (Box WO-17)
      - A Change of Luck, undated (Box WO-17)
      - Dared and Done: Elizabeth Barrett and Robert Browning's Marriage, 1994-1995 and undated, 3 versions in 6 folders; folder 3 is print (Box WO-17)
      - The Fiery Nadar Took Paris' Pulse (print), 1995 May (Box WO-17)
      - Two Years After His Death, The Curtain Rises on Andy Warhol (print), 1989 February (Box WO-17)
      - On Location, 1987 June and undated, 2 versions in 2 folders; folder 2 is print (Box WO-17)
    - Marschall, Richard
      - The Tough Coughs as He Ploughs the Dough (proposal), undated (Box WO-17)
    - McCall, Lillian
      - Untitled Non-Fiction Book 1984 January and undated, 6 versions in 7 folders (Box WO-17)
        (folder 3 has Saul Bellow's handwritten corrections)
    - McCully, Emily
      - A Life Drawing, undated, 1 version in 2 folders (Box WO-17)
    - McDermott, Alice (Box WO-18)
      - At Weddings and Wakes, undated, 3 versions in 6 folders (Box WO-18)
      - Deliveries (print), 1980 July (Box WO-18)
      - Romantic Reruns (print), 1979 August (Box WO-18)
      - She Knew What She Wanted, 1985-1986, 2 folders; folder 2 is print (Box WO-18)
      - The Simple Truth (print), 1978 July (Box WO-18)
      - Small Lasses (print), undated (Box WO-18)
      - Summer Folk (print), 1981 April (Box WO-18)
      - Sweetest, Sweeter, Sweet (print), undated (Box WO-18)
      - That Night, undated, 2 versions in 3 folders (Box WO-18)
      - Two Book Reviews (print), 1986 and undated (Box WO-18)
    - McMahon, Thomas
      - Bell and Langley (print), 1985 Summer (Box WO-18)
      - Loving Little Egypt, 1985-86, 1992, and undated), 5 versions in 7 folders (Box WO-18)